We'll be ready in just as strong.
On the four public input, I'm getting personal appearances.
Five, discussion, and possible action items.
Item A, MSU aid claims list.
Motion to approve.
Second.
Easton, circle.
Jones.
Hi.
Barnes.
I'm Parker.
Hi.
I'm B.
Goodell, Stratton, Edmunds, and Palmer Claim for Pensacola,
GRDA, relicencing, and associated complaint proceeding in the amount of $165.
Yes, if you don't mind board, I'll just talk about both of them.
Then, and also the hall, I still claim.
This is for our GRDA civil litigation.
So, you know, Goodell Stratton and Edmund, they kind of had them in on a couple of meetings with us.
Obviously, Hall Estell was the one that helped us kind of come with our wording for the settlement,
came to some meetings, attended the final meeting, and everything.
So, if it's approved, we'll have a remaining balance of $731,451.10, if both of these are approved tonight.
That's the money that we budget for the year.
Let's do approve.
I'll second.
Easton.
Hi.
Jones.
Barnes.
Hi.
And C is the Hall Estell claim for GRDA civil litigation amount of $8,255.70.
Make motion approved.
Second.
Jones.
Hi.
Barnes.
Easton.
Hi.
Thank you.
Gee.
Okay.
overs.
Thank you.
From fueled.
Well done.
Bet.
Mm.
Thank you, Mrs Losling.
Thank you.
Okay.
Switch.
Time out.
Looking forward to the next meeting.
Okay.
We'll be shortly.
What this is is S sub 2, we redid it about six years ago, and what's one of the sub 2?
S sub 2 is the one over by Nivell's house.
The big one?
Yeah, yeah.
So it's different than the other ones we have, it's a double breaker.
There's two breakers that run off each feet or one relay controls those two breakers.
We've had some issues with a transfer scheme on that, it's not operating up to a potential
level, and what this is going to do is allow it to do that, it's the engineering portion
of that, and it takes in the count of the timing of breakers if we lose feet on one bus
and we'll transfer the other.
There's still outages, there's still be a blank involved with that, so it's not like it
doesn't, but it does blank and transfer the other so that people will have power.
With that, it also makes sure we're not peeping out to transmission side and then transfers
back to the other one, to the, to as normal, it also has to do some timing issues because we
don't want every breaker all unclosing at once, so there's a timing aspect to that also.
So after they do the commissioning or the settings part of it, they'll come down to actually
install those settings and commission and actually test it, make sure it's actually operating
the way we actually need it to.
Or we're going to need this for the new meters anyway?
Nope, this has nothing to do with the meters itself, it's just for the, the relays, what
the relays do is control the breakers so that each meter is going on at all.
So kind of like the make of the easy way to look at it is, it's a really cool design,
there's two different transformers and we have two different feeds from GRDA, so with the
updated settings, if the one feed from GRDA goes down, then everything on that one transformer
will be able to transfer over to the other transformer.
So that was all new, both six years old.
With this upgrade, are we going to do this in other six years?
Maybe because you got to think, I mean, this stuff is happening in less than a second,
I mean, we're talking about cycles, so I mean, you know, electronics go bad, they, you know,
they change, so we're in essence updating the electronics and the programming and everything
else.
So it's a really cool, I mean, our industrial customers like it feeds a lot of our industrial
customers because it keeps them, so basically it's going to keep us from having more
out of it or, yeah, whenever there is an outage, they'll only be out for a few seconds with
this one.
Yeah, hopefully, you know, if the, like, if one feed from GRDA goes down, then we'll be able
to transfer the whole load over to the other transformer and then we would not have an outage
for those customers.
Motion to approve.
Thank you.
Hi.
Jones.
Chairman, trust.
The Solid Waste Department is purchasing a trash truck to replace a 10-year-old truck.
The 10-year-old truck will now be used as a backup.
We went out to four different lending institutions and first national bank came in, the lowest
speeding the next closest bidder by $500.58.
We recommend setting up a lease purchase contract
with First National, and we need you to approve.
Without getting really close, isn't it?
They came in real close, and they've been getting closer
and closer on most of these deals.
Like a motion we approve.
Once again.
East deck.
Jones.
My barns.
Five.
Don't go further.
Thank you.
Sixth.
Other new business.
If any, what's the reason that's supposed to be this agenda?
Seven trustee community announcements.
Eight trust manager communications.
Just let the board know that our AMI meters are out for bid right now.
So we'll open bids November 13th.
I'm unless you know that we have some kind of extension or something.
So that'll be good.
I'm open bids.
Then obviously review with vendors.
The different, you know, the different options.
And then hopefully present something around the first year for the board to approve.
And then get them hopefully, you know, start sending them to the city, start installing.
That's all I have.
I'm not in a German motion.
Second.
Go both.
All right.
Third.
Five.
Jones.
East.
Five.
Marker.